Office of the Registrar, School of Medicine Records UA075
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Grade files, 1973 -- 2013; UA075.003; 13.2 Linear Feet
  - Applied Learning Exp. MPH453 Fourth Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00079 (Box 104)
  - Biostatistics in Public Hlth. MPH132 First Year, 2010 -- 2011; UA075.003.104.00080 (Box 104)
  - Epidemiology & Biostats II MPH112 First Year, 2010 -- 2011; UA075.003.104.00081 (Box 104)
  - Hlth. Care Org: Budget & Mgmt. MPH136 First Year, 2010 -- 2011; UA075.003.104.00082 (Box 104)
  - Hlth. Srvc. & Public Hlth. MPH137 First Year, 2010 -- 2011; UA075.003.104.00083 (Box 104)
  - Integration of Public Hlth.MPH151 First Year, 2010 -- 2011; UA075.003.104.00084 (Box 104)
  - Social & Behavioral Org. MPH118 First Year, 2010 -- 2011; UA075.003.104.00085 (Box 104)
  - ALE: Planning Seminar MPH253 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00086 (Box 104)
  - Hlth. Behavior & HCOM MPH289 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00087 (Box 104)
  - Integration of Public Hlth. MPH251 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00088 (Box 104)
  - Intro. To Env. & Occ. Hlth. MPH203 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00089 (Box 104)
  - Intro. To SAS MPH265 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00090 (Box 104)
  - Law & Public Health MPH204 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00091 (Box 104)
  - Public Hlth. Field Exp. MPH208 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00092 (Box 104)
  - Research Method MPH288 Second Year, 2011 -- 2012; UA075.003.104.00093 (Box 104)
  - Adolescent Hlth. MPH305 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00094 (Box 104)
  - Applied Epi: Analyzing the Bio Lit MPH355 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00095 (Box 104)
  - Applied Learning Exp. MPH353 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00096 (Box 104)
  - Case Studies in Hlth. & Human Rights MPH377 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00097 (Box 104)
  - Clin. Epi. Of Cardiovascular Dis. MPH392 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00098 (Box 104)
  - Ethics & Law in PH MPH354 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00099 (Box 104)
  - Hlth. Care Reform & More MPH357 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00100 (Box 104)
  - Integration of Public Hlth. MPH351 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00101 (Box 104)
  - MH in a Public Hlth. Context MPH359 Third Year, 2012 -- 2013; UA075.003.104.00102 (Box 104)
- Additional accessions, 1900-1975; UA075.004
  - Medical School: Registrar's Office student records, 1950 -- 1962; UA075-001 (Box 1)
  - Medical School: Registrar's Office student records, 1950 -- 1974; UA075-002 (Box 2)
  - Microfilm student records, 1900 -- 1975; UA075-003 (Box 3)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Reel 74-1 has a break that could not be repaired as of October 2021.